

CONTACT DETAILS

donna.bartolome2008@gmail.com (+63) 9082932160

To deliver measurable business results by using my project management expertise, analytical skills, and user experience background. Through planning and insightful reporting, I aim to support the organization in achieving its digital objectives and maximize online success.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF FINE ARTS - ADVERTISING College of the Holy Spirit Mendiola, MNL

INTERMEDIATE

La Consolacion College Mendiola, MNL

SKILLS & PROFICIENCY

HTML • CSS • Bootstrap
WordPress • CSCart • MailChimp
Adobe Creative Suite • Sketch • Figma
JQuery • Javascript
JIRA • Trello • AzureDevOps
MS 365 Utilities • Google Utilities

TRAININGS AND WORKSHOPS:
ISO 9001:2008: Quality Assurance &
Documentation
Risk Management Process Management
Waterfall Proj. Management Methodology
Agile Proj. Management Methodology

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Quantrics Enterprise Inc.

Sr. Web Developer | Dec2022 - Present

RESPONSIBILITIES:

- 1. Effectively maintain web interfaces and features, ensuring they remain performant, accessible, secure, and compatible across various platforms and browsers.
- 2. Create HTML and CSS templates adhering to responsive design framework standards.

ShopFrontPro Inc.

Project Manager - Operations | Sept2020 - Sept2022

RESPONSIBILITIES:

- 1. Collaborate with cross-functional teams, including designers, developers, and stakeholders to define project objectives.
- 2. Responsible for establishing visual reports, charts, and graphs to communicate production performance, efficiency, and quality metrics to stakeholders, enabling data-driven decision-making and promoting a deeper understanding of production processes.
- 3. Monitor and track key performance indicators (KPIs) to assess the effectiveness and success of project initiatives.
- 4. Develop and maintain project documentation, including project plans, and status reports.

Sr. UX Designer /Front-end Developer | Dec2015 - July2022

RESPONSIBILITIES:

- 1. Identifies areas for improvement, recommending changes or enhancements, and implementing strategies to enhance user experience, conversion rates, and overall website performance.
- Successfully managed end-to-end website development projects from prototyping to deployment, ensuring optimized cross-browser and multi-platform compatibility.
- 3. Standardize all frontend outputs, leveraging modern design techniques and strategies by adopting a responsive, mobile-first approach.
- 4. Leads training aimed at coaching clients and newly hired personnel about the Company's content management system and process workflows.

Freelance Web Designer Graphic/ Web UI Designer | Feb2014 - Sept2015

DirectWithHotels Inc.

Production Manager | Dec2010 - Feb2014

RESPONSIBILITIES

1. Develop and maintained a comprehensive set of key performance indicators (KPIs) aligned with production goals.



CONTACT DETAILS

donna.bartolome2008@gmail.com (+63) 9082932160

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

- 2. Collaborate with cross-functional teams to develop strategies and initiatives based on KPI insights, driving continuous improvement and achieving production targets.
- 3. Ensures the timely completion of projects by utilizing project management tools and applications to allocate resources, formulate strategies, and closely track project progress.
- 4. Conducts comprehensive quality assurance checks on all projects to ensure adherence to established quality standards and timely delivery of products.

DirectWithHotels Inc. Sr. Web Designer | 2008 - 2010

RESPONSIBILITIES:

- 1. Provides assistance and support to the Production Manager in evaluating project requirements on a daily basis.
- 2. Serves as a mentor to junior associates, including designers, writers, and online marketing associates, offering guidance on training, UI principles, and project objectives.
- 3. Develops and maintains a comprehensive project documentation, such as project plans and project status reports, to ensure effective project management and communication.

Associate Designer | Apr2006 - 2008

RESPONSIBILITIES:

- 1. Accountable for delivering 100 hotel websites within a six-month timeframe.
- 2. Consistently achieved a 100% Net Promoter Score and received Total Performance Appraisal ratings of 90% or higher on a quarterly basis, reflecting excellent performance.

Boma One Pacific Graphic Artist/ Jr. Web Designer | 2004 - 2006